Yes! I'll keep you hooked on Ikiri World whether you're asleep or awake! This is Yukiyuki Wrinkle, a.k.a. Ikiri!
Let's go!
I've been meaning to tell you this somewhere.
I've been meaning to tell you this somewhere, but in March, on a show called "Countdown TV Live Live
AKB's new song "Jutte kimi ga suki dakidatta" was performed for the first time.
We had a lot of lessons at night for about a week before the first performance.
We all choreographed together.
This song is not a dance song at first glance.
but it was a bit difficult and intense, and we had a lot of things to do together.
After quite a few lessons...
There's an interlude after the second chorus, right?
There's a pretty intense dance part there.
First there are 3 dancers, then 2 dancers, then 5 dancers, and so on.
Then two more came out, then five, and so on...
I don't know why I was chosen.
It was really difficult.
We practiced a lot, especially there.
I really worked hard.
We were dancing for 4 hours straight.
The night before the performance, the last rehearsal.
Let's do it like it's the last performance.
So, to be honest, I did it.
We're going to do it tomorrow, so let's do it like it's the last performance.
Everyone took off their masks.
We looked at our faces in the mirror and decided to do it right.
During the interlude, when we were doing our very best...
Suddenly
I couldn't get my strength back.
I felt like something was wrong with my body.
It was either my legs or my back.
But we were doing it with sound and we were filming.
I was thinking, "Oh my God, I'm in trouble.
I was thinking, "Oh my God, I'm going to have to cross the street.
After it was over, I felt like I'd been pushed through.
I need a cane, so I'm walking with an umbrella or something.
But I can't walk much and it hurts.
And I thought, "Oh no.
I did it the day before, the first time I got tired.
The next day, after fitting for the costume.
I decided to go to the hospital.
And then...
I was like, "Oh, wow.
And then I was like, "Okay.
I have a separated leg between my hip and leg.
Wow!
Give me a break!
I get it.
It's a separation, right?
Yes, yes, it's true that at that moment...
I was thinking that it looked like a separation.
But the doctor...
He said, "That's unusual.
I haven't seen this kind of separation in a long time.
What do you mean? I said.
This is where nightclub dancers get torn muscles.
He said something like that.
I think that's what he was thinking.
It's very twisted like this.
Like pulling.
Like, "Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here...
I probably overdid it on the part where I had to use a lot of force.
I think I overdid it and separated my lower back and legs.
And the doctor said
It might take a week and a half to two weeks.
I don't know.
First of all, I'm going to show for the first time tomorrow.
And I'll be taped up.
I'll see how it goes, but I definitely want to go out.
So I sat through the lesson that day.
The next day, when I woke up in the morning...
Hmm?
Surprisingly, it came out.
I went to the hospital.
On the way to the hospital.
What? I thought he was going to say something about how he was feeling better.
So I asked him to take a look.
And the doctor said...
What? It's like...
It's so much better than yesterday!
Mr. S. said right away...Soon, Mr. S.
I feel better!
Mr. S. said...
You're just resilient, aren't you?
Heh heh heh heh.
I really am.
I get injured easily and get sick easily.
But anyway...
I recover at an unbelievable speed.
It was the same when I was sick.
But this time, before I performed for the first time.
I was feeling pretty good.
That's why I could dance.
It's a zero balance.
You do it right away...
I'll do it right away, but I'll get it back.
Yuuka-san... Yuuka-san...
Yes!
What?
I knew it too.
I don't have any abs or anything.
These legs are the only thing stopping me.
I've been working out.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
I mean, it's just, you know...
Like, for a photo book, or for Grovia, or...
But I thought it would be a pain in the ass.
I thought I'd just do a little bit at home.
But now it's time...
I'm not doing it for the way I look, but for the foundation of my body.
I'm doing it for the foundation of my body
I'm not talking about how I look, but where I ended up.
I was on a shopping show once.
Here's a Mac!
Sixpad!
Cool pack! Pads!
You bought some of those, right?
There it is.
Let's start with that.
Once, first.
I thought I'd start with that.
I'm going to change the subject.
There's on-vegetables, right?
I love on-vegetables so much.
I also go there with Mr. S.
I'm also going with my best friend Yufuko, who's also on YouTube.
Haruka Katayama, who's also on YouTube with my best friend Yufuko.
I often go to On-yasai.
And the last time I went to Ong Vegetable
When I was taking it to the cashier at the end
on the slip
like they do at Starbucks or something.
like "Thank you" or something like that.
I don't know, sometimes it's like
You know what I'm talking about.
and they write "Thank you" or "A" on the slip.
or "A" for me, you know?
on a veggie slip with a "Thank you" written on it.
and it was for one person.
And the manager brought it to me quite a few times.
He was very nice.
He would go to Ong Vegetable about once a week.
So I finally went to Ong Vegetable too much.
I thought, "Oh, I've been served. I thought.
Okay.
What? Isn't it great? It's like...
He said there's a service with vegetables on it.
So I went to pay.
I have to say thank you.
What's this? Like, "What's this?
I said, "For one.
Thank you so much.
It was totally my fault! He said...
What? Like that.
I wasn't a celebrity or anything!
It was so embarrassing.
It was the waiter's mistake.
It was only for one simple person.
Thank you's are just thank you's.
It was nothing.It was nothing.
I talked to her after we left.
Seriously, I probably didn't even notice.
I don't think I'm ready for this yet.
It was really embarrassing.
You know how they have self-checkout machines now?
When my mom paid at the self-checkout...
When your mom paid at the self-checkout, the receipt paper got cut off.
And when the receipt didn't come out...
The clerk would come after her.
If the receipt doesn't come out
she might not have paid.
That's what it means.
My mother
She made me suspicious.
So, she asked me to give her contact information.
I'll have to check things out.
I gave them my contact information.
Mom left.
I'll check it out, and maybe that's it.
It looks like they're looking at security cameras.
And it beeps.
Your mom's on the camera.
She was cleared of all charges.
For a moment, I thought she was...
She was accused of shoplifting.
I remember that... now.
And... it's really not important.
This is just a short episode.
Premium Music?
You know, the one that came out the other day?
When I collaborated with Mr. Fujimori of Flying Get
I collaborated with Mr. Fujimori of Flying Get
I sent him a DM saying I'd watch the premium music.
Everyone is looking forward to the premium music!
I really, really don't give a shit.
It's super trivial.
I'm not saying I'm watching premium music.
I'm watching premium panties.
I'm so tired!
I don't even know what that means anymore.
What do you mean?
I'm tired.
Just looking at it.
Huh.
What are premium panties?
It's kind of funny.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
What are premium panties?
Oh... I had it all squished...
I thought if I erased them, I wouldn't need them anymore.
My premium panties!
Oh!
There they are!
Proof.
Oh!
snowflakes
Premium panties.
Look at the whole thing.
Oh, my God, it's a surprise worker modus operandi.
Damn.
So here we go.
I have a flesh separation today.
But don't worry.
I'm really doing great!
Because as you can see from the TV
I can dance to the beat of my own drum.
And I'm going to concerts.
so please don't worry.
and the story of my misunderstanding at the on-air festival
I received a DM for premium panties.
I sent you a three-part series.
That's all for now.
See you soon!